// const dayTwoQuestions = [
//   {
//     question: "Does Islam blame women for the fall of man from paradise?",
//     options: [
//       "Yes, similar to Christianity and Judaism, Islam also blames women for the fall of man",
//       "Only men are blamed in Islam",
//       "No, Islam does not blame women for the fall of man from paradise",
//       "None of the above",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 2,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "How should women be treated in Islam?",
//     options: [
//       "Women should be treated as slaves",
//       "Women are considered as bad omens and sinful",
//       "Women be treated with respect, honour and justice. It condemns oppression of any kind",
//       "None of the above",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 2,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "Does Islam teach about the right to education for women?",
//     options: [
//       "The right to education is only for men",
//       "There is no education system in Islam",
//       "In Islam, seeking knowledge is mandatory for every Muslim (both men and women)",
//       "None of the above",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 2,
//   },
//   {
//     question:
//       "Can women hold important positions in governments or politics in Islam?",
//     options: [
//       "No, women cannot hold any important positions in government",
//       "Yes, women can hold important positions in government and politics",
//       "Only men are allowed to hold important positions in government",
//       "No one can hold positions in government",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 1,
//   },
//   {
//     question:
//       "Are women allowed to remarry in Islam after divorce or death of the husband?",
//     options: [
//       "Yes, remarriage for women is permitted in Islam",
//       "No, remarriage is not permitted for women in Islam",
//       "Only men have the right to remarry",
//       "None of the above",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 0,
//   },
//   {
//     question:
//       "What did the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) mention about the raising of daughters?",
//     options: [
//       "Anyone who raises two daughters with love and affection will enter paradise",
//       "Daughters are ill omens and should not be given love and affection",
//       "There is no mention about the raising of daughters by the Prophet (PBUH)",
//       "None of the above",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 0,
//   },
//   {
//     question:
//       "What did the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) mention about the status of a Mother?",
//     options: [
//       "Mothers are not important at all",
//       "Paradise is beneath the feet of a mother",
//       "Mothers are bad omens",
//       "None of the above",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 1,
//   },
//   {
//     question:
//       "What is mentioned about the equality of men and women in the Quran?",
//     options: [
//       "Men are always superior to women in all aspects",
//       "Women are always superior to men in all aspects",
//       "Men and women have the same religious and moral duties and responsibilities",
//       "None of the above",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 2,
//   },
//   {
//     question:
//       "Does Islam permit women to inherit the property or a share of the property from their parents?",
//     options: [
//       "Yes, both men and women are entitled to a specified share of the property left behind by their parents or close relatives",
//       "Only men can inherit the property of the parents and close relatives",
//       "The property left behind is offered in charity to the poor",
//       "None of the above",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 0,
//   },
//   {
//     question:
//       "Do Muslim women have the right to accept or deny marriage proposals?",
//     options: [
//       "Muslim women have full rights to accept or deny marriage proposals",
//       "Muslim women cannot choose their suitors",
//       "Parents of the bride have the right",
//       "None of the above",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 0,
//   },
// ];

// export default dayTwoQuestions;
const dayTwoQuestions =[
  {
    question: "Which of the following sunnah fasts give the reward of fasting the entire year?",
    options: ["Fasting every alternative day", "Fasting every day", "Fasting on the day of Arafah", "Fasting 6 days in Shawwal"],
    correctOption: 3,
    justification: "Whoever fasts Ramadan and follows it with six days of Shawwaal, it will be as if he fasted for a lifetime. (Muslim)"
  },
  {
    question: "Whoever prays Isha in congregation has the reward of…?",
    options: ["Praying the entire night", "Praying half of the night", "28 times the reward of a person praying alone"],
    correctOption: 1,
    justification: "Whoever attends Isha prayer in congregation, then he has the reward as if he had stood half of the night. (Tirmidhi 221)"
  },
  {
    question: "Whoever prays Isha and Fajr in congregation, then he has the reward of…?",
    options: ["Praying the entire night", "Praying half of the night", "28 times the reward of a person praying alone"],
    correctOption: 0,
    justification: "Whoever prays Isha and Fajr in congregation, then he has the reward as if he had spent the entire night standing in prayer. (Muslim 656a)"
  },
  {
    question: "According to a hadith, what caused Prophet Muhammad (SAW) to forget Laylatul Qadr?",
    options: ["Some people were fighting", "Some people were quarreling", "Some people asked him other questions"],
    correctOption: 1,
    justification: "Two men among the Muslims started quarreling, so (the knowledge) was taken away. (Bukhari 49)"
  },
  {
    question: "When should we seek out Laylatul Qadr in Ramadan?",
    options: ["On the last 10 nights of Ramadan", "On the odd-numbered nights of the last 10 nights of Ramadan", "On the 27th night of Ramadan"],
    correctOption: 1,
    justification: "Seek Laylat al-Qadr among the odd-numbered nights of the last ten nights of Ramadaan. (Bukhari 2017)"
  },
  {
    question: "Who are the 3 people whose dua is not rejected?",
    options: ["Fasting person at iftar, just ruler, and traveler", "One who gives sadaqah, the oppressed, and the sincere person", "Fasting person at iftar, just ruler, and oppressed person"],
    correctOption: 2,
    justification: "There are three whose du’aa’ is not rejected: a just ruler, the fasting person when he breaks his fast, and the prayer of the oppressed person. (Tirmidhi 2525)"
  },
  {
    question: "If someone fasts for the sake of Allah, they will be distanced from the Hellfire by how many years?",
    options: ["50 years", "60 years", "70 years", "80 years"],
    correctOption: 2,
    justification: "Whoever fasts a day in the way of Allah, Allah will move his face away from the Hellfire by a distance of seventy years. (Bukhari 2685, Muslim 1153)"
  },
  {
    question: "Which door of Jannah is made specially for those who fast?",
    options: ["Baabul-Al-salath", "Baabul jihad", "Baabul sadaqat", "Baabur Rayyan"],
    correctOption: 3,
    justification: "In Paradise, there is a gate called Al-Rayyan, which none will enter but those who fast. (Bukhari 3017)"
  },
  {
    question: "The first action a servant of Allah will be held accountable for on the Day of Resurrection is…?",
    options: ["Prayers (Salah)", "Reading the Quran", "Fasting", "Jihad"],
    correctOption: 0,
    justification: "The first action for which a servant of Allah will be held accountable on the Day of Resurrection will be his prayers. (Tirmidhi 413)"
  },
  {
    question: "On which day did the Battle of Badr take place?",
    options: ["15th Ramadan 3 A.H", "17th Ramadan 2 A.H", "10th Ramadan 1 A.H"],
    correctOption: 1,
    justification: "The Battle of Badr took place on 17th Ramadan 2 A.H. (Ilmfeed)"
  }
];
export default dayTwoQuestions;